we're gonna practice the same yesterday
meeting you have a deal younger we're
gonna hammer loot out of hockey
[Music]
taisho sanke the - hi - you mama sure
the sure you show yard said hi Alphonse
no decency to a judge my mother me
[Music]
Kesha that of a Holliman
then we'll start with small know you
gotta find shelter
jungbaek I should relax your mouth only
to holiness don't you may show Phu Phu
small smile
wait shout Josh other way show I relaxed
mph found so no fingers Irene eyes so
shoulders go back
hola
and then we'll come to our breath no
light on who she shall long exhales
childhood she put your mind on your
breath in the same way to shop at Whole
agenda gentle gentle eater who sees how
to and to Tahoe Caesar
then please and invite one of your
teachers she may be your mom
even our shitty currency which it was a
multi attribute allows you to give her
nothing
today in Benton Kenichi Miyajima
McKinney charge
didn't think of something you love about
this person this is like a baton to them
just to record something you admire you
can tell attention to me
please don't make any noise be sitting
still
then think of something you did in the
last day or two which was not very nice
maybe you were irritated and someone
else here is a quadrillion total around
tm+ a hard City back in nature now to
the janitor I'll shut up I've had seen
it
then let your teacher know about
something really nice you've done
then ask your teachers to keep teaching
know how much things you need allows you
shouldn't tell anyone around you give us
trouble can I see
then ask our teacher to stay in our life
changed a woman I couldn't
we're so close to meditation pray for
don't wait hot outta someone not so
close you may open even to someone who's
not so close
a permit to the kingdom seen
there's no
and I said did something terrible
it was injured I shouldn't talk about
that that's the warranty ladies let me
pay her back it's a good thing to do
let me do my best to make her happy she
wanted until she unpacked I seen
saturation
should I put in today for example this
is step 5 other people and myself equal
right to my time parents agenda Kingdom
in the future if I don't if I only focus
you know
this is first time
I put in there.put yourself and
then let's look at those feelings in
their hearts
in the
I believe
then let's give them let's give them our
attention take some deep breaths fire
stations and
golden I think I like to add the smell -
ha - away beauty if you'd have a me it's
leaving from my nostrils to go other
people and coming to their house about
harming their see me coming down their
throat having a hole
take your time but I don't world this is
my meditation time the things I have to
do my meditation
when we're selfish
a virus a new way to treat people eating
so the final status to enjoy away any
progress
so may be due to some kind of light for
other people good example
enjoy being a good example we hope on
you